skillrack.com 2010-11-25

# Privacy policy of SkillRack.com

This privacy policy sets out how SkillRack.com uses and protects any information that you give SkillRack.com when you use this website. SkillRack.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy statement. 

SkillRack.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 21-October-2010. 

**What we collect?**

What we collect We may collect the following information: Name and job title contact information including email address 

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:   
-Internal record keeping.   
-We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

**Commitment to Spam prevention**

There will be no bulk email notifications for newsletter or any kind of marketing activity. 

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees and hiring companies (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. 

**How we use cookies**

The website may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Controlling your personal information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you.If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email to **contact@SkillRack.com**. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at **contact@SkillRack.com**. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us at the above email address. 

**Accountability to information maintained by user**

We hold no accountability for any user entered information (similar but not limited to questions, exams, tutorials etc) through our application or through any external links.
